Inventory of the Mills E. Godwin Jr. Papers 1947-1989
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of Mills E. Godwin Jr., 1947-1978. (Box-folder 1-15:1-325)
  - Correspondence of Mills E. Godwin, Jr., 1978. (Box-folder 15:321-325)
    - Correspondence of Mills E. Godwin, Jr., February-April 1978. (Box-folder 15:325)
      Letters to Governor and Mrs. Godwin regarding service to Virginia; correspondence on Mrs. Godwin's book, Living in a Legacy; news article, "Godwin Described as Great, Popular" by Governor John N. Dalton; letters on administration; Republican Party of Newport News resolution expressing gratitude to Godwin.
  Series 2:Correspondence of Katherine B. Godwin
- Correspondence of Katherine B. Godwin, 1966-1976. (Box-folder 15-16:1-14)
  This series begins with an article from the Virginia Record of January, 1966, entitled "First Lady of the Commonwealth." It gives much information regarding Mrs. Godwin, Governor Godwin, and their daughter, Becky. Other correspondence includes certain highlights of includes certain highlights of Mrs. Godwin's official, personal and social activities during her husband's public life.
  Other material related to Mrs. Godwin is scattered throughout the entire collection, and the items comprising this series constitute a small portion of the total amount of her correspondence in the Godwin Papers since she personally handled the bulk of her correspondence.
  - General Correspondence, 1966. (Box-folder 15:1)
    Virginia Record article on Mrs. Godwin occupying Mansion; letters regarding invitations.
  - General Correspondence, January-July 6, 1967. (Box-folder 15:2)
    General Correspondence, invitations and visits to Mansion.
  - General Correspondence, July 7-July 31, 1967. (Box-folder 15:3)
    Correspondence regarding automobile accident July 2, 1967, Waynesboro, Virginia, state limousine driven by Trooper Shields; correspondence regarding medical services and insurance; personal letters, confinement at University of Virginia Hospital and recovery.
  - General Correspondence, August-December, 1967. (Box-folder 15:4)
  - General Correspondence, January-December, 1968. (Box-folder 15:5)
    Statement by Mrs. Godwin, Honorary Chairman of Library Week; invitations, letters on participation in Virginia Jaycee project - "Apply Jelly Sunday"; news release regarding Mrs. Godwin's operation at Norfolk General Hospital; letters regarding Honorary Chairman of Lee District Junior Woman's Club; cancellations following Becky's accident; acknowledgments of cookbooks received.
  - General Correspondence, January-December, 1969. (Box-folder 15:6)
    Message as Honorary Chairman of Woman's Auxiliary, Richmond Academy of Medicine: information sent to Charleston, South Carolina paper; statement on work of Richmond Symphony Women's Committee; honorary chairmanships; invitation from Mrs. Lyndon Johnson; note from Mrs. Hubert Humphrey; letters on leaving Mansion.
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1975. (Box-folder 15:7)
    Biographical information on Mrs. Godwin; complimentary letters on Mrs. Godwin as First Lady of Virginia; letters of appreciation by St. John's Church members regarding Mansion reception; articles and pictures on the Godwin's new home at Cedar Point; article on Mrs. Godwin and campaign; The Journal, article on Mrs. Godwin; newspaper article regarding "Miniature First Ladies Show Of Ballgowns"; gifts to Mrs. Godwin; acknowledgments of gifts received.
  - General Correspondence, 1976. (Box-folder 15:8-9)
    Mrs. Godwin's calendar and participation in various events; invitations, acknowledgments of cookbooks; introduction of Elizabeth Hanford Dole, wife of Senator Robert J. Dole of Kansas, Williamsburg; U. S. Department of Commerce Award to Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission; Garden Clubs coffee; Christmas Mansion tours and information
    - General Correspondence, January-June 1976. (Box-folder 15:8)
    - General Correspondence, July-December 1976. (Box-folder 15:9)
  - General Correspondence (Box-folder 15:10-11)
    Invitations; participation in various events; requests and responses from organizations for donation of items for auctions; Thalhimer's appearance to autograph Living in a Legacy; Virginia State Chamber of Commerce information and purchases of Mrs. Godwin's book; letters regarding book.
    - General Correspondence, January-June 1977. (Box-folder 15:10)
    - General Correspondence, July-December 1977. (Box-folder 15:11)
  - General Correspondence, 1978. (Box-folder 15:12)
    Acknowledgments of Mrs. Godwin's book, Living in a Legacy; letters of appreciation for Mansion tours and gifts; correspondence regarding depletion of supply of Mrs. Godwin's book.
  - Activities, 1974-1977. (Box-folder 15:13)
    Chronological order of Mrs. Godwin's activities, 1974-1977; dinners and receptions, 1974-1977; numerical information on number of people touring Mansion.
  - Frankie Welsh Scarf, 1974-1976. (Box-folder 15:14)
    Correspondence and information on Frankie Welsh Scarf designed for Mrs. Godwin for use as gift; letters acknowledging receipt of scarf.
  Series 3: Correspondence of Becky Godwin
- Correspondence of Becky Godwin, 1957-1974. (Box-folder 16:1-5)
  This correspondence includes letters, news articles and general information relating to Becky Godwin, beginning with her early school days and continuing through 1968. Included among the material is her diary written in March and April, 1963, covering a European trip she made with her mother and father, who was then lieutenant-governor.
  - General Correspondence, and Diary of European trip, 1957-1966. (Box-folder 16:1)
    Letter from Godwin enrolling four-year old daughter in First Baptist Church Nursery during legislative session; lieutenant-governor and Mrs. Godwin leave for Virginia Cruise of Mediterranean; news article and pictures; diary of trip personally written by Becky (March-April, 1963); Godwin's letter to bank regarding Becky's checkbook; letters relating to attendance at Camp Sequoya, Sullins College, Bristol, Virginia.
  - General Correspondence, 1967. (Box-folder 16:2)
    Acknowledgment of V.M.I. sweater sent to Becky; Godwin's letters to Becky at Camp; acknowledgments of gifts to Becky; letter to Becky regarding Mansion ghosts; Becky's letter requesting information for a school project.
  - Correspondence of Becky Godwin, 1968. (Box-folder 16:3-4)
    Letter and application for Becky to return to Camp Sequoya; acknowledgments of gifts; Godwin's letter to Camp Sequoya Director enclosing Becky's spending money and other letters to Becky while at Camp; correspondence thanking Virginia Beach Hospital for assistance given Becky as result of bicycle accident; letters regarding Becky's accident and death.
    - General Correspondence, January-September 1968. (Box-folder 16:3)
    - General Correspondence, October-December 1967. (Box-folder 16:4)
      Accident and Death; Condolences; Memorials.
  - General Correspondence; Condolences; Memorials; December 1969-1974. (Box-folder 16:5)
    Continuing letters of sympathy; offer of placement of wreath on Becky's grave by Meadowbrook Memorial Gardens President; presentation of trophy by Alexandria Department of Recreation in Becky's memory; letters regarding memorial fund at St. Catherine's School; acknowledgment and copy of SJR #2 - "On the Death of Becky Godwin"; Becky Godwin Memorial Fund established at Oakland Christian Church and memorial gift by Men's Bible Class of Chuckatuck; correspondence on and acknowledgment of portrait of Becky; song written in memory of Becky by Viet Nam veteran; establishment of Becky Godwin Water Skiing Memorial at Camp Sequoya by Governor and Mrs. Godwin; poem in Becky's memory and other memorial gifts; establishment of Becky Godwin Fund, School of Nursing, Medical College of Virginia; purchase of confirmation robes, St. John's United Church, in memory of Becky; books donated in Becky's memory; correspondence regarding scholarship award to Paul D. Camp Community College in Becky's memory by the Herbert Perkinsons; Virginia Education Association Award in Becky's memory for yearly scholarships.
  Series 4: Schedules
- Schedules, 1966-1978. (Box 16)
  This series consists of official appointment and engagement books compiled during Godwin's two gubernatorial terms, 1966-1970 and 1974-1978. Also included are his major appointments as a private citizen for the years 1971, 1972 and 1973.
  - First Term Schedules,. (Box-folder 16:1-2)
    - Daily Schedule Book, January-December 1966. (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Daily Schedule Book, 7 May-31 July 1968. (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Private Citizen Schedules, 1971-1973. (Box-folder 16:2)
    Monthly calendars.
    - Monthly Calendar, January-December 1971. (Box-folder 16:2)
      Shows major appointments and engagements.
    - Monthly Calendar, January-December 1972. (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Monthly Calendar, January-December 1973. (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Second Term Schedules,. (Box-folder 16:3-15)
    - Appointment Book, January-December, 1974. (Box-folder 16:3)
      Shows daily appointments and engagements by date and hour insofar as practical.
    - Typed daily schedule sheets, 1975. (Box-folder 16:4-5)
      Typed daily schedule sheets, filed monthly. Also includes advanced weekly and monthly appointments.
      - Typed daily schedule sheets, January-June 1975. (Box-folder 16:4)
      - Typed daily schedule sheets, August-December 1975. (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Appointment book, January-December 1975. (Box-folder 16:6)
      Appointment book, desk copy. Daily and hourly appointments and engagements reflecting late changes, adjustments, etc.
    - Declined Invitations, 1975. (Box-folder 16:7)
      File showing invitations declined by the governor during the year.
    - Typed Daily Schedule Sheets, 1976. (Box-folder 16:8-9)
      Typed daily schedule sheets. Filed monthly as above with advanced weekly and monthly schedules.
      - Typed daily schedule sheets, January-June 1976. (Box-folder 16:8)
      - Typed daily schedule sheets, July-December 1976. (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Appointment Book, January-December 1976. (Box-folder 16:10)
      Appointment book, desk copy, listing daily and hourly appointments and engagements where applicable.
    - Governor's Daily (office) Schedule Sheets, January-December 1977. (Box-folder 16:11-13)
      Governor's daily (office) schedule sheets in folders by month. Shows office appointments and other engagements. Preliminary weekly and monthly schedules also included.
      - Governor's daily schedule sheets, January-March 1977. (Box-folder 16:11)
      - Governor's daily schedule sheets, April-June 1977. (Box-folder 16:12)
      - Governor's daily schedule sheets, July-December 19767. (Box-folder 16:13)
    - Appointment Book, January-December 1977. (Box-folder 16:14)
      Appointment book - daily and hourly appointments (generally more accurate than sheets). Travel plans listed separately when applicable
    - Daily schedule sheets, 1-13 January 1978. (Box-folder 16:15)
  Series 5: Speeches
- Speeches, 1957-1978. (Box 17-24)
  This series contains Godwin's official speeches, as well as other formal speeches made as a private citizen from 1957 through 1977. Although Godwin was a popular speaker prior to 1957, especially during his active participation in Ruritan National and early days in the General Assembly, no copies of speeches given during that period have survived.
  - Speech, 5 September 1957., 1 item. (Box 17)
    Prepared Statement to the State Highway Commission of Virginia advocating the North-South Route for the Chesapeake Bay Bridge and Tunnel.
  - Speeches, 1961., 3 items. (Box 17)
    - Hanover Civic Associations, Ashland, Virginia, Candidate for Lieutenant governor of Virginia, 27 May 1961. (Box 17)
    - Sound Government Speech, June 1961. (Box 17)
    - Excerpts from remarks to the Young Democratic Club of Norfolk, Norfolk, Virginia, Candidate for lieutenant-governor, 7 June 1961. (Box 17)
  - Speech, 4 July 1962., 1 item. (Box 17)
    Excerpts from remarks at Historic St. John's Church, Richmond, Virginia, in connection with ceremonies sponsored by American Heritage Foundation.
  - Speech, 8 November 1963., 1 item. (Box 17)
    Remarks made to the Representatives of the Sigma Delta Chi at Williamsburg, Virginia.
  - Speeches, 1965., 14 items. (Box 17)
    - Statement announcing his candidacy for the Democratic Nomination for governor of Virginia, 9 January 1965. (Box 17)
    - Northern Neck Electric Cooperative, 11 August 1965. (Box 17)
    - Virginia High School Editors, Richmond Professional Institute, Richmond, Virginia, 27 August 1965. (Box 17)
    - Remarks at the home of Bruce Green, Arlington County, Virginia, 7 September 1965. (Box 17)
    - Christopher Newport College Dedication, Newport News, Virginia, 11 September 1965. (Box 17)
    - Carroll County-Grayson County Barbecue and Political Rally, Galax, Virginia, Lieutenant-governor of Virginia and Democratic Nominee for governor, 18 September 1965. (Box 17)
    - District Q, Virginia Education Association, Henrico High School, Democratic Candidate for governor, 23 September 1965. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Press Women, Thomas Jefferson Inn, Charlottesville, Virginia, 2 October 1965. (Box 17)
    - Virginia State Grange, Hotel Jefferson, Richmond, Virginia, 9 October 1965. (Box 17)
    - District R, Virginia Education Association, Courtland, Virginia, Democratic Candidate for governor, 11 October 1965. (Box 17)
    - Political Speech, The Dome, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 21 October 1965. (Box 17)
    - Holiday Inn, Marion, Democratic Banquet, Democratic Candidate for governor, 23 October 1965. (Box 17)
    - Statement by Governor-elect Godwin on day following election, 3 November 1965. (Box 17)
    - Tidewater Rehabilitation Institute, Norfolk, Virginia, 2 December 1965. (Box 17)
  - Speeches, 1966., 96 items. (Box 17)
    - Inaugural Address, 15 January 1966. (Box 17)
    - Address to General Assembly, 17 January 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Soil Fertility Association, Hotel John Marshall, 27 January 1966. (Box 17)
    - Georgia-Pacific Dedication, Emporia, Virginia, 31 January 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Forest Incorporated, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond Regional Conference on Education, Mary Washington College, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 2 February 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Earl Gregg Swem Library and Charter Day at College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia, 12 February 1966. (Box 17)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner Introduction of the Speaker, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, 19 February 1966. (Box 17)
    - John Tyler Technical College Ground Breaking, 24 February 1966. (Box 17)
    - State Young Democratic Clubs Convention, Annual Banquet, 19 March 1966. (Box 17)
    - Keysville Plant Dedication, Danville Industries, Keysville, Virginia, 25 March 1966. (Box 17)
    - Georgia-Pacific Plant Dedication, Emporia, Virginia, 4 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Lynchburg Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting, 13 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Installation Ceremonies, James Madison Inn, Phi Delta Phi University of Richmond School of Law, 15 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Old Dominion Advertising Conference, Virginia Press Association Midtown Motor Hotel, Danville, Virginia, 16 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Annual Meeting, Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, Hotel John Marshall, 19 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, Hotel Jefferson, Richmond, Virginia, 20 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Southeastern Theatre Conference, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 21 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Airtronics Plant Dedication, Fairfax County, 26 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, Twelfth Annual Dinner, Marriott Twin Bridges Motor Motel, 26 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication, New Products Division, American Tobacco Company, Bermuda Hundred, 29 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Introduction of Mr. Justice Hugo Lafayette Black of the Supreme Court of the United States, Mt. Vernon, Virginia Law Day, 30 April 1966. (Box 17)
    - Agency Head Luncheon Group, Hotel Richmond, Richmond, Virginia Hopewell Democrats, 2 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Union Camp Corporation Plant, Jefferson Davis Highway, Chesterfield County, Virginia, 10 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Seminar on Economic Development, Martha Washington Inn, 11 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Omicron Delta Kappa, Hampden-Sydney College, Farmville, Virginia, 12 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Associated Press Broadcasters, Executive Motel, Richmond, Virginia, 13 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Twentieth Annual Meeting, Roanoke River Basin Association, The Downtowner, Danville, Virginia, 18 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication Technical Center, Allied chemical Corporation, Interstate 95, 19 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Newcomen Society Dinner, Introduction of E. Claiborne Robins, 19 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Reston, Reston, Virginia, 21 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Prelude to Independence, 28 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Frederick College Commencement, Norfolk, Virginia, 30 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - June-is-Dairy-Month Luncheon, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 31 May 1966. (Box 17)
    - Southside Virginia Economic Seminar, Longwood College, Farmville, Virginia, 2 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of Picnic Shelter, Fairy Stone State Park, Martinsville, Virginia, 5 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - Mathews High School Commencement, 7 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - General Electric Plant, Lynchburg, Virginia, 11 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - VMI Commencement, Lexington, Virginia, 12 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - Boys' State, Phi Beta Kappa Memorial Hall, Williamsburg, Virginia, 13 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Association of Broadcasters, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 17 June 1966. (Box 17)
    - The Lane Company Plant Dedication, Altavista, Virginia Greetings, 16 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - The Lane Company Plant Dedication, Altavista, Virginia Remarks, 16 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Traffic Safety Study Commission, 18 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - Introduction of Sir Patrick Dean, Jamestown, Virginia, 22 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - Home Builders Association of Virginia, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 25 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - Buchanan County Chamber of Commerce, Breaks Interstate Park, 28 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - Introduction of Sir Patrick Dean, Virginia State Bar Association Annual Meeting, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 30 July 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Association of Electric Cooperatives, Golden Triangle, Norfolk, Virginia, 3 August 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia State AFL-CIO Convention, Roanoke, Virginia, 29 August 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, Williamsburg, Virginia, 16 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - State Campaign Kickoff Dinner for Byrd-Spong, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, Young Democratic Clubs of Virginia, 17 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - Testimonial Dinner for The Honorable Howard W. Smith, Warrenton Armory, 23 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication of the Portsmouth Armory, 25 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Day Luncheon, Virginia State Fair, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 27 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - Eastern Shipper-Motor Carrier Council, Hotel John Marshall, 28 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - Safety Awards Luncheon, Holiday Inn West, Richmond, Virginia, 29 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication Exercises, Buffalo Creek Watershed Project, Lake Jimmy Gayle, Prince Edward County, Virginia, 30 September 1966. (Box 17)
    - VPI-West Virginia Football Game, Blacksburg, Virginia, 1 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Conference on Education, The Mosque, Richmond, Virginia, 5 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Closing Remarks, Governor's Conference on Education, The Mosque, Richmond, Virginia, 5 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - "The Subject Was Roses", Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Richmond, Virginia, 11 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Gunston Hall Board of Regents, Gunston Hall, 12 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Joint Dedication of the Petersburg Information Center and America House, Washington Street Exit, Interstate 95, Petersburg, Virginia, 13 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - 1966 Fall Conference of the Bank of Virginia, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 14 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Capital Outlay Conference Virginia Association of Counties, Natural Bridge Hotel, 17 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Union Camp Corporation Plant Expansion, Franklin, Virginia, 19 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Architectural Woodwork Institute, Williamsburg, Virginia, 20 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Eighteenth Annual World Trade Conference, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 20 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Conservation Award Dinner, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 21 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Steering Committee, Governor's Conference on Education, 25 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Buena Vista Industrial Foundation, 26 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - E. R. Moore Dedication, Buena Vista, Virginia, 26 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Nelson Manufacturing Plant Dedication, Lovingston, Virginia, 26 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - U. S. Plywood-Chesapeake Corporation Plant Dedication, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 28 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - General Electric Dinner, Commonwealth Club, 31 October 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Hospital Association, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 3 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Education Association Convention, The Mosque, Richmond, Virginia, 3 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Elon College, Elon, North Carolina, 5 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - The United Daughters of the Confederacy General Convocation, Hotel Jefferson, Richmond, Virginia, 7 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - State Auxiliary Luncheon, Y.W.C.A., 9 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Southern State Cooperatives Annual Meeting, The Mosque, Richmond, Virginia, 10 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - DECO- Westinghouse Dedication Leesburg, Virginia, 14 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Coleman Furniture Company Dedication, Pulaski, Virginia, 15 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Electro Plastic Fabrics, Pulaski, Virginia, 15 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Pulaski County Chamber of Commerce, 15 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Fifth Annual Luncheon for New York Travel Writers, Editors and Directors of Travel, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York, 17 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - "Report to Top Management", Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, 18 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller Luncheon, Colonial Williamsburg, 19 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - Thanksgiving Festival Reenactment, Berkeley Plantation, 20 November 1966. (Box 17)
    - The Virginians" Dinner, Del Monico's Hotel, New York City, 2 December 1966. (Box 17)
    - Ingersoll-Rand Plant Luncheon, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 5 December 1966. (Box 17)
    - Brotherhood Citation Dinner, Richmond Chapter, National Conference of Christians and Jews, Hotel John Marshall, 7 December 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication Ceremonies - Virginia Beach (section of highway system), 8 December 1966. (Box 17)
    - Appreciation Luncheon, Southern Conference, Hotel John Marshall, 9 December 1966. (Box 17)
    - Dedication, Gordon Avenue Branch, Charlottesville, Virginia, McIntire Public Library, 12 December 1966. (Box 17)
    - Governor's Christmas Message, Christmas 1966. (Box 17)
  - Speeches, 1967., 109 items. (Box 17-18)
    - Committees on Privileges and Elections, 5 January 1967. (Box 17)
    - Budget Preview, 6 January 1967. (Box 17)
    - Moneta Dress Corporation, Bedford County, 10 January 1967. (Box 17)
    - Twenty-eighth Annual Meeting, Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Districts, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 10 January 1967. (Box 17)